ANJALI MISHRA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Senior Consultant with 6 years' experience in Software Quality Assurance Testing. Adept in collaborative problem solving, risk management and creative solutions. Advanced background in anticipating user behaviors and providing the solution to improve product quality for various software applications.

WORK HISTORY

Senior Consultant, 06/2021 - Current Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited, Hyderabad, Telangana

- Championed continual process improvements at board meetings by offering 6 years' industry experience and expertise.
- Troubleshot complex operational issues by diagnosing root causes and devising effective solutions.
- Encouraged development of clear objectives and action plans.
- Drafted Test Plan which included testing objectives, testing phases, scenarios, and test environment after a thorough analysis of the business rules.
- Involved in test cases review by the development team, and product management and modified the test cases based on their feedback.
- Responsible for planning, executing, and managing the UI automation scripts for AngularJS applications using Webdriver IO and Mocha Testing Framework to provide better regression test coverage.
- Created manual testcases, and reviewed with different stakeholders to validate the functionality, so that it meets the expected business criteria.
- Performed functional testing to identify various critical points in the application.

Consultant, 06/2018 - 06/2021

Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited, Hyderabad, India

- Participated in requirement understanding and developing usecases.
- Drafted functional scenarios and testcases to provided better coverage of the functional requirements and reviewed with team

- P Hyderabad, India 91
- 8008213546
- anjalimarch24@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anjali-mishra-38494925

SKILLS

- Software Testing: Functional Testing, Automation Testing
- Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha, Cucumber
- Design Patterns: Page Object Model, Behaviour Driven Development
- Functional Testing Tool: Selenium
 WebDriver/Grid, Protractor,
 Webdriver IO, Cypress
- API Testing Tool: Rest Assured
- Technologies/Domain: US Tax
 Process, Hospitality, Fleet
 Management System
- Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, Apache POI
- Web Technologies: Angular JS, Node.JS
- Scripting: Java, JavaScript
- IDE: Eclipse, VS Code
- Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha
- Web Debugging Tool: XPath, Firepath, Firebug
- Build Tool: Maven
- Processes: Agile-Scrum, Waterfall
- Bug Tracking Tools: JIRA, VSTS, QTest
- Continuous Integration Tools: Jenkins, Azure Devops
- Version Control: GIT
- DataBase: SQL Server
- Operating Systems: Windows

lead.

- Shared test reports with various test metrics with team members and team lead, to have a clarity on quality control.
- Automated functional testcases by using Selenium Web-Driver and TestNG testing tools.
- Developed scripts for data driven framework using Selenium WebDriver, TestNG and Apache POI API.
- Used Maven to build and run the Selenium automation framework shared consolidated automation test reports.

Software Testing Engineer, 04/2016 - 06/2018

Cybage Software, Hyderabad, India

- Effectively determined automation testing needs through Selenium Webdriver.
- Continually improved team processes from Requirement Gathering to Test Closure.
- Utilized JIRA and VSTS to perform manual testing through test suites. Participated in all phases of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), its methodologies such as Agile, SCRUM.
- Involved in understanding the business requirements of the customer and developed testcases.
- Developed, modified, and executed scripts.
- Implemented Generic Functions and Project specific Functions in Libraries, in Automation test framework built using Page Object Model design pattern.
- Customized scripts using parameterization techniques.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology, 07/2008

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University - Lucknow

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Applause Award 2022

• Got Applause award for automating MyInsight CE using Webdriver IO.

Innovation Champion Award 2021

• Got recognized for building a proof of concept for automating webservices using Rest Assured.

Spot Award 2019

• Got recognized for automating MyInsight CE using protractor tool.

Spot Award 2022

• Got recognized with spot award for delivering the essential test metrics and providing support to peers and new hires.

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level		